[
	{
		"question": "At what rate do people who are cyberbullied tell their family or someone they trust about being cyberbullied?",
		"answer": "10%",
		"description": "Only one in ten people who are cyberbullied tell others about it. That's a pretty small percentage, isn't it?"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the percentage of peope who stated that they were threated in an online game is?",
		"answer": "47%",
		"description": "Almost one in two people who play online games experience cyberbullying."
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the rate of cyberbullying among young people in the world?",
		"answer": "50%",
		"description": "One in every two young people is cyberbullied. Even one of your friends can be a cyberbullying victim!"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the rate of students being exposed to cyberbullying in school groupchats?",
		"answer": "70%",
		"description": "7 out of 10 people in a class groupchat have been cyberbullied in some way. Cyberbullying is everywhere!"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the rate of cyberbullying victim knowing the cyberbully?",
		"answer": "64%",
		"description": "Since cyberbullying occurs over the internet, we think it is often done by someone we do not know. How high is the rate of finding someone we know!"
	},
	{
		"question": "At what rate are adults being cyberbullied?",
		"answer": "40%",
		"description": "Children and teenagers are not the only ones who are subjected to cyberbullying. One in three adults experience it too!"
	},
	{
		"question": "At what rate is cyberbullying seen on social media?",
		"answer": "65%",
		"description": "Social media platforms are places where cyberbullying is more common. More than half of social media users are exposed to cyberbullying!"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the rate that people experience cyberbullying about their appearance? ",
		"answer": "61%",
		"description": "More than half of people care about their appearance (height, weight, clothing style, etc.) and experience are bullied about it online!"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the rate of exposure to cyberbullying on social media applications in one day around the world?",
		"answer": "38%",
		"description": "Roughly one in three people are exposed to some form of cyberbullying in a day"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the sharing rate of people who take a screenshot of someone else's post or photo and share it wihout permission?",
		"answer": "35%",
		"description": "Roughly one in three people's photos or posts are shared without permission!"
	}
]
